{
  "Conflicting Information":{
    "200":{
      "answer":"What type of conflict is a land dispute?",
      "question":"As simple conflict",
      "team":""
    },
    "400":{
      "answer":"Jealous of a co-worker getting a pay raise, an employee of a company shoots down his co-worker’s product designs.  What type of conflict is this?",
      "question":"Ego conflict",
      "team":""
    },
    "600":{
      "answer":"A group wants to raise money for a charity.  One member suggests an extensive internet campaign.  Another member proposes a bake sale.  What type of simple conflict is this?",
      "question":"Process conflict",
      "team":""
    },
    "800":{
      "answer":"Two employees of a construction company are debating how to lay a foundation.  One employee insists he knows the most efficient way as he has been on many similar jobs before.  What is the cause of this conflict?",
      "question":"Knowledge",
      "team":""
    },
    "1000":{
      "answer":"What are the 5 causes of conflict?",
      "question":"Perception, Personality, Knowledge, Culture, Power and Status, and Procedural Expectation",
      "team":""
    }
  },
  "Horrible Bosses":{
    "200":{
      "answer":"Stems from a position that isn’t clear",
      "question":"What is a Pseudo Conflict?",
      "team":""
    },
    "400":{
      "answer":"Groupthink",
      "question":"What is something that prevents good, idea generating conflict?",
      "team":""
    },
    "600":{
      "answer":"Horrible seating arrangements",
      "question":"What is a way to ensure ego conflicts at a meeting?",
      "team":""
    },
    "800":{
      "answer":"When workers are often pitted against one another to the point where they resent each other and their boss",
      "question":"What is too much conflict?",
      "team":""
    },
    "1000":{
      "answer":"Conflict is a bad thing",
      "question":"What is false?",
      "team":""
    }
  },
  "In the mix":{
    "200":{
      "answer":"Having the role of central negative is also known as playing… ",
      "question":"What is “devil's advocate”?",
      "team":""
    },
    "400":{
      "answer":"An anonymous system to help brainstorm ideas and weed out ego conflict",
      "question":"What are computer mediated messages?",
      "team":""
    },
    "600":{
      "answer":"Ruins interpersonal relationships and group morale",
      "question":"What is Unresolved Conflict?",
      "team":""
    },
    "800":{
      "answer":"A decision about decision",
      "question":"What is Metadiscussion ?",
      "team":""
    },
    "1000":{
      "answer":"The 5 conflict management styles",
      "question":"What are Avoidance, Accommodation, Collaboration, Compromise, Competition?",
      "team":""
    }
  },
  "Straight outta Beebe":{
    "200":{
      "answer":"To have high concern for both yourself and others in your group",
      "question":"What is collaborate?",
      "team":""
    },
    "400":{
      "answer":"The illusion of agreement within groups",
      "question":"What is groupthink?",
      "team":""
    },
    "600":{
      "answer":"Some conflict is inevitable in groups, but this does not mean that all group discussions are doomed to end in disagreement. Conflict can be managed.  “.....” occurs when all group members support and are committed to a decision",
      "question":"What is Consensus?",
      "team":""
    },
    "800":{
      "answer":"An expressed struggle between at least two interdependent people who perceive incompatible goals, scarce resources, and interference from others to achieve specific goals ",
      "question":"What is conflict?",
      "team":""
    },
    "1000":{
      "answer":"When you do X, in situation Y, I feel Z",
      "question":"What is the X,Y,Z formula?",
      "team":""
    }
  },
  "Cinematic Conflict":{
    "200":{
      "answer":"The conflict between Juror #3(The last holdout) and Juror #5(The less well off man)",
      "question":"What is Simple Conflict",
      "team":""
    },
    "400":{
      "answer":"The conflict between Kovack and everyone else regarding throwing Willi overboard",
      "question":"What is simple Conflict?",
      "team":""
    },
    "600":{
      "answer":"The conflict management style used by everyone when the turned away from the Racist Juror",
      "question":"What is conflict avoidance?",
      "team":""
    },
    "800":{
      "answer":"This conflict type was exemplified by Kocvac and Willi throughtout the movie Lifeboat",
      "question":"What is Ego conflict?",
      "team":""
    },
    "1000":{
      "answer":"The conflict management style used by Juror #8 after he called for a secret ballot and said he would not stand in the way of a guilty verdict.",
      "question":"What is conflict avoidance?",
      "team":""
    }
  }
}
